(Sheldon:)Go east.
"An iron gate blocks your way."
(Sheldon:)Open gate.
"It's locked."
(Leonard:)Hmm.
(Sheldon:)Well, so much for that.
(Leonard:)It's getting pretty late.
How come you're still up?
I found an emulator online that
lets you play classic text-based
(Sheldon:)computer games from the 1980s.
(Leonard:)That's pretty cool.
(Sheldon:)Oh, yes. It runs on the world's
most powerful graphics chip:
(Sheldon:)imagination.
(Leonard:)You've really got
to get out more.
(Sheldon:)Go north.
"You can't go that way."
(Sheldon:)Go west.
"A troll blocks your passage."
(Sheldon:)Okay. Fasten your seatbelts.
(Sheldon:)Kill troll.
"With what?"
(Sheldon:)With sword.
"You don't have the sword."